Matthew Charles

UX/UI Desinger

majacha21@gmail.com

Personal Profile

I am very approachable and a reliable individual who enjoys working in creative team environments. I am reflective and honest with myself about my work. I have a passion for User Experience and User Interface design, and it is something I intend to progress further with.

Experience

Bristol Rovers

Bartender

October 2023 - Present

- · Serving customers with drinks
- Helping with sorting stock and making sure each bar has enough for gamedays.

Testo - testing supplies

Warehouse / store room assistant (agency work VIA Personnel Selection)

August 2023 – September 2023

 Pick packing - making sure contents of packages are in good condition and have correct certifications.

Oakley Health Group

Administrator / Receptionist (temporary position)
June 2021- September 2021, June 2022 – September 2022:

 Front desk reception – checking patients in, dealing with queries, taking messages, updating information on the clinical system.

Education

University of West England, Bristol September 2020 – Present BSc (Hons) Digital Media

The Sixth Form College Farnborough September 2018 – June 2020 Business Studies A Level Grade (B) Medieval History A Level Grade (B) Biology A Level Grade (C)

Skills

IT Skills

Microsoft Office, HTML, CSS, JavaScript including 3.js and p5.js, Figma, Webflow

Team Work

I have worked well in teams, from playing football (I was also made captain a few times), to doing group work at university. I always pull my weight and take the initiative.

Communication

When communicating with people I always try to make sure that communication is clear. Double checking what has been said and agreed upon before the conversation ends.

Responsibility and Organisation

I am a very reliable and hard working person who takes pride in their work. I take responsibility for I do. I am punctual and always meet deadlines for projects.